<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Suresh Kumar Gadi</title>
    <link>https://suresh.ml/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Suresh Kumar Gadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2017 Suresh Kumar Gadi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 23:34:04 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://suresh.ml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Variable stiffness mechanism</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/projects/variable-stiffness-mechanism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 23:34:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/projects/variable-stiffness-mechanism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In vel ligula tortor. Aliquam erat volutpat.
Pellentesque at felis eu quam tincidunt dignissim.
Nulla facilisi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pellentesque tempus nisi et interdum convallis.
In quam ante, vulputate at massa et, rutrum
gravida dui. Phasellus tristique libero at ex.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One day workshop on LaTeX</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/posts/One-day-LaTeX-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/posts/One-day-LaTeX-workshop/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This workshop presents an introduction to the programming language LaTeX  for the first time users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe style= &#34;height: 480px; width: 100%;&#34; src=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B6A_I6W9HjBDb29KdUJsZXFYblU/preview&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-files&#34;&gt;Other files&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;requirements&#34;&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A PC with the following software installed. Or having a good Internet connection to work with ShareLaTeX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest version of TeXLive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A LaTeX IDE (Ex. TeXstudio)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;venue&#34;&gt;Venue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facultad de Contaduría y Administración, Blvd. Revolución 151 Ote., Torreón, CP 2700&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;time&#34;&gt;Time&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9AM to 2PM on 16th June 2016&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Digital</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-Control%20Digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 23:12:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-Control%20Digital/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secondary school certificate (SSC)</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 1999 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/education/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Suresh Kumar Gadi obtained secondary school certificate in the march month of the year 1999 from the board of secondary education Andhra Pradesh (AP). He carried out his education in the city Visakhapatnam. He scored an average of 75.4%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Secondary school certificate&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;June 1999&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Ramakrishna residential public school&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;Visakhapatnam&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>