<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work-experiences on Suresh Kumar Gadi</title>
    <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work-experiences on Suresh Kumar Gadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 23:12:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://skgadi.com/work-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Research professor</title>
      <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/uadec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 23:12:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/uadec/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research professor</title>
      <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/upa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 23:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/upa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test engineer (Project trainee)</title>
      <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/htsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 23:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/htsl/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;Accomplishments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed a factory floor tester (FFT) for an HVAC (heating, ventilation, and air conditioning) controller. The device under test (DUT) (i.e. HVAC controller) is placed inside an FFT. The FFT needs to verify all the specifications of the HVAC controller, like digital &amp;amp; analog inputs and outputs, Light emitting diodes (LED), resistance measurement etc. This is the final test done by the manufacturer before packing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed the software part of the FFT for a Remote monitoring unit (RMU)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tested many electronic devices for sending a feedback to the designing section and also performed tests to prepare the products to the standards of CE (Conformité Européenne) and FCC (Federal Communications Commission). These tests include testing the specifications, the temperature range, the humidity range, the mechanical shock range, the radiation immunity range etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field specialist</title>
      <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 23:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/slb/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;Accomplishments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obtained Schlumberger&amp;rsquo;s Xpert certification in SWT. SWT is a testing process of an oil well usually performed on an oil rig, which starts at flow head and runs all the way to burners. Since SWT crew is responsible for bringing the oil to the surface for the first time, the safety of the personnel, the oil-well and the equipment is of very high priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xpert certification includes a training on the selection of equipment for a given SWT project. Since offshore rigs are having limited space on deck, planning the right amount of the spares for immediate on-site maintenance is required to reduce the down time of the oil rig. Click here to see the original certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience in operating and maintaining the SWT equipment like flow-head, sand filter, choke manifold, heat exchanger, separator, surge tank, burner etc. Also, got trained in operating and maintaining pressure gauges, temperature gauges, and pressure recording devices of different models.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Performed in-house inspection for the SWT equipment.
Worked with the SWT teams at many offshore and onshore including some HTHP (high temperature and high pressure) wells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;appreciation&#34;&gt;Appreciation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dennis MCrystal, instructor at Schlumberger’s ELC (European learning center), Paris in the year 2006 commented:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suresh has been a consistent performer during the course. He is very good at putting theory into practice and gets the job done in a professional and safe manner (proactive as safety officer). He is very motivated and dedicated and this shows in his results. His reporting skills are very strong which proves good attention to the finer details. He could be more assertive and openly confident in his abilities. With experience and confidence, he could be a key figure in the SWT (Surface Well Test) crew.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer (Electrical)</title>
      <link>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/lnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2005 23:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skgadi.com/work-experience/lnt/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;Accomplishments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construction of the 66 KV double circuit transmission lines at Bawana, Delhi

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervised the complete site work and undertook the planning part of the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for generating reports to the higher management like job cost report (JCR) and material reconciliation report etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handled the sub-contractor and client billing. Followed up client billing until the accountant receives the check from the client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for generating the reports tallying the work done (or the material supplied), the remaining work (or the remaining material to be supplied), the amendment required, the work billed for the subcontract (the amount paid to the suppliers) and the invoiced work to the client (or the invoiced material to the client).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed a software in FoxPro to reconcile the site data where the material consumed by a subcontractor was easily tracked. This software generates reports in a user-friendly way (MS Excel and HTML), which was of great use since the software used by the company was lacking the certain functionality to track the material based on the work done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed another software to generate a stringing chart based on a statistical analysis performed on the data received from the R&amp;amp;D department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Railway electrification project from Ludhiana to Amritsar in Punjab

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Along with a senior staff supervised foundation and erection of masts, stringing of catenary and contact conductor, erection of ATD (auto tension device) and other accessories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construction of the 132 KV double circuit transmission lines at Jodhpur, Rajasthan

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Along with a senior staff supervised foundation, erection, and stringing of the transmission line tower. The site work also includes handling client visits at the site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for maintaining the material consumption reports and tallying with the store records.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>