<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Suresh Kumar Gadi</title>
    <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Suresh Kumar Gadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2017 Suresh Kumar Gadi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 23:12:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://suresh.ml/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Digital</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-circuit-analysis-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 23:12:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-circuit-analysis-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Digital</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-control-digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 23:12:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-control-digital/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>