<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Home</title>
    <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2017 Suresh Kumar Gadi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 23:12:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://suresh.ml/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Digital</title>
      <link>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-Control%20Digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 23:12:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suresh.ml/courses/2016-07-12-Control%20Digital/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here. Content is here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>